<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Su</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sam Su</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Yiheng Su</title>
      <link>/post/2021/01/23/cs373-spring-2021-yiheng-su/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/01/23/cs373-spring-2021-yiheng-su/</guid>
      <description>1. Where did you grow up?
I grew up in Shenzhen, China, then immigrated to the US (Plano, TX) around 2012. Learning English as a second language was tough growing up, but my middle school days were some of the best in hindsight.
2. What high school did you attend?
I attended Liberty HS in Frisco, TX. Go Redhawks!
3. What was your favorite extracurricular activity in high school?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reticulate Fun with Python!</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/03/reticulate-fun-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/03/reticulate-fun-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Python has always been a popular tool for a variety of reasons. However, I believe that R has the edge in certain applications, such as data visualization using ggplot.
Below, we are going to analyze some data from python first, then use R to visualize what we will learn!
# need reticulate to start communicating!library(reticulate)Here, we load the boston dataset and conduct a Principal Component Analysis to identify meaningful clusters of houses in Boston</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction and MotivationAnyone who has worked in the industry has been in the following scenario: you work hard to be promoted for X position, while in the end some competitor Y gets promoted to the position instead. You feel annoyed; you feel that it’s unfair! Y is clearly way less suitable than you are for this position! Y must have cheated or hitched a deal with the boss!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionI have always loved reading, so I thought may not use R and data science to help me decided which book I should read next! After poking around on Kaggle, I have found two datasets containing a myraid of information on many titles. The first dataset by Soumik originated from him scraping the GoodReads API using ISBNs and contains the variables ‘bookID’ (a unique integer associated with each book), ‘title’, ‘authors’, ‘average rating’ (0-5 scale), ‘isbn’, ‘isbn13’, ‘langauge code’ (eng or other languages), ‘num_pages’, ‘ratings_count’ (total number of ratings), ‘text_reviews_count’ (total number of written text reviews).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  --</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>object data=“/resume.pdf” type=“application/pdf” &amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
