<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sam Su</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sam Su</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Week of 25 Jan - 31 Jan</title>
      <link>/post/2021/01/30/cs373-blog2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/01/30/cs373-blog2/</guid>
      <description>1. What did you do this past week?
I attended lectures on Monday, Wednesday, and Friday this past week. During those lectures, I learned a lot about the assertions (assert), unit testing frameworks (unittest), and coverage tools (coverage) in python3 under the context of the Collatz Conjecture, a century old problem that no one has yet to prove, yet always holds nevertheless. Quite surprising, since the problem is fairly easy to understand as compared to other millennium questions such as ‘Does P = NP’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Yiheng Su</title>
      <link>/post/2021/01/23/cs373-spring-2021-yiheng-su/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/01/23/cs373-spring-2021-yiheng-su/</guid>
      <description>1. Where did you grow up?
I grew up in Shenzhen, China, then immigrated to the US (Plano, TX) around 2012. Learning English as a second language was tough growing up, but my middle school days were some of the best in hindsight.
2. What high school did you attend?
I attended Liberty HS in Frisco, TX. Go Redhawks!
3. What was your favorite extracurricular activity in high school?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reticulate Fun with Python!</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/03/reticulate-fun-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/03/reticulate-fun-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Python has always been a popular tool for a variety of reasons. However, I believe that R has the edge in certain applications, such as data visualization using ggplot.
Below, we are going to analyze some data from python first, then use R to visualize what we will learn!
# need reticulate to start communicating!library(reticulate)Here, we load the boston dataset and conduct a Principal Component Analysis to identify meaningful clusters of houses in Boston</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
