<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sam Su</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sam Su</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Week of 11 Mar - 28 Mar</title>
      <link>/post/2021/03/27/cs373-blog9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/03/27/cs373-blog9/</guid>
      <description>1. What did you do this past week?
This past week, me and my group have been working hard to attempt to finish up phase II of the project, namely implementing by the backend RESTful API, pulling data from a deployed MySQL database in AWS, and then finally consuming that API in the frontend in an attempt to display the data nicely in a paged format. We had finished almost all of the backend requirements, but we are still somewhat stuck on pagination as well as unit testing around the board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Week of 8 Mar - 14 Mar</title>
      <link>/post/2021/03/12/cs373-blog8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/03/12/cs373-blog8/</guid>
      <description>1. What did you do this past week?
This past week, in addition to attending lectures, I met with my team to get a head start on phase II of the project. Currently, we have a MySQL database created and hosted on AWS RDS, whereby the tables (and schemas) in that database are dynamically created via code in SQLAlchemy. The learning curve was definitely smaller compared to learning React and JSX from scratch, but again Structured Query language is an entirely different beast on its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Week of 1 Mar - 7 Mar</title>
      <link>/post/2021/03/07/cs373-blog7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/03/07/cs373-blog7/</guid>
      <description>1. What did you do this past week?
This past week was most definitely the busiest week, given that phase I of the website project was due yesterday. We had to figure out how to write a fourteen page MPA from scratch, decorate it with various media, and then deploy it for production in AWS. Of course, as Dr. Downing had mentioned, the class material is purposely designed to exhibit a large disconnect from the tools and skills required to implement the project, so that we had almost zero experience diving head straight into the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Week of 22 Feb - 28 Feb</title>
      <link>/post/2021/02/28/cs373-spring-2021-yiheng-su/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/02/28/cs373-spring-2021-yiheng-su/</guid>
      <description>1. What did you do this past week?
This past week, I attended lectures as usual and learned operators and the reduce() function in Python. Also, I have been busy with our team working on phase I of the large website project. Because of the past storm, we couldn’t really get together as a team until Saturday of this week where we finished the project proposal on natural disaster education and prevention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Week of 1 Feb - 7 Feb</title>
      <link>/post/2021/02/05/cs373-blog3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/02/05/cs373-blog3/</guid>
      <description>1. What did you do this past week?
Since I had already finished the first project (Collatz), I really didn’t do anything much this past week besides attend the regularly scheduled lectures. However, after learning about the possibility of other solutions to the problem such as employing an eager or a meta cache, I might experiment with those over the weekend.
2. What’s in your way?
So far I am smooth sailing in juggling classwork and research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Week of 25 Jan - 31 Jan</title>
      <link>/post/2021/01/30/cs373-blog2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/01/30/cs373-blog2/</guid>
      <description>1. What did you do this past week?
I attended lectures on Monday, Wednesday, and Friday this past week. During those lectures, I learned a lot about the assertions (assert), unit testing frameworks (unittest), and coverage tools (coverage) in python3 under the context of the Collatz Conjecture, a century old problem that no one has yet to prove, yet always holds nevertheless. Quite surprising, since the problem is fairly easy to understand as compared to other millennium questions such as ‘Does P = NP’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS373 Spring 2021: Yiheng Su</title>
      <link>/post/2021/01/23/cs373-spring-2021-yiheng-su/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/01/23/cs373-spring-2021-yiheng-su/</guid>
      <description>1. Where did you grow up?
I grew up in Shenzhen, China, then immigrated to the US (Plano, TX) around 2012. Learning English as a second language was tough growing up, but my middle school days were some of the best in hindsight.
2. What high school did you attend?
I attended Liberty HS in Frisco, TX. Go Redhawks!
3. What was your favorite extracurricular activity in high school?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reticulate Fun with Python!</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/03/reticulate-fun-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/03/reticulate-fun-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Python has always been a popular tool for a variety of reasons. However, I believe that R has the edge in certain applications, such as data visualization using ggplot.
Below, we are going to analyze some data from python first, then use R to visualize what we will learn!
# need reticulate to start communicating!library(reticulate)Here, we load the boston dataset and conduct a Principal Component Analysis to identify meaningful clusters of houses in Boston</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
